smart-publications.com 2010-01-23

# Smart Publications Privacy Policy

Recent Articles

Commentary

Dear Mr. Morgenthaler, 

Thank you for the _“Health & Wellness Update.”_ I look forward to each issue, and the solid information it provides.

\- John V.   
Sun City, AZ 

Praise for  
Smart Publications _  
Health & Wellness Update_

"For sometime now I have enjoyed reading Smart Publications. They are beautifully structured, well written and educational"

\- John W.   
Durham, NC 

"Wealth of information for anyone that chooses alternative healing methods. It's an education in itself just to read one of these newsletters! Every time I get one I read it from cover to cover! Easy to understand and easy to decipher when looking for products. Well done! It's a joy to read."

\- B. White   
Oxnard, CA    
| 

## Smart Publications Terms of Use & Privacy Policy

Smart Publications (SP) is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**   
We automatically collect your Internet service provider's address, the web page from which you came, and a record of your activity on our site. 

In addition, Smart Publications invites viewers to sign up for both/either our monthly printed newsletter or our email newsletters. Smart Publications Health & Wellness Updates are groundbreaking newsletters filled with articles, interviews and reviews of the best sources for hard-to-get health supplements. Each issue also shares recent scientific research and tips on ordering life-extending pharmaceuticals and smart drugs at tremendous savings and without a prescription. When you sign up for a Smart Publications Health & Wellness Update subscription, we collect information that you volunteer such as your name, email address, and postal address to process your order. Subscriptions can be canceled at any time. 

**Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate**   
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please contact us with the new information or your review request. 

**Data Release**   
Smart Publications will abide by this privacy policy except as required by subpoena, search warrant or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to a member, non-member or others. 

**Cookies**   
Smart Publications' Internet website uses "cookies". Cookies are messages that a Web server transmits to a Web browser so that the Web server can keep track of the user's activity on a specific Web site. The message that the Web server conveys to the browser is in the form of an HTTP header that consists of a text-only string. The text is entered into the memory of the browser. The browser in turn stores the cookie information on the hard drive so when the browser is closed and reopened at a later date the cookie information is still available. We use this information to collect demographic information such as frequency of user visits and the amount of time spent on the website. 

**Links to Outside Websites**  
Smart Publications' privacy policy applies only to its website. Our website may contain links to outside sites. Please be aware that other sites operate under their own privacy policies and that these sites may collect your personal information. Smart Publictions claims no responsibility for the data collection policies of outside websites. 

**Notification of Changes**  
In the event that Smart Publications should change its privacy practices or start using member information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we would notify our customers of the changes, explaining the reasons and allowing them the opportunity to accept the changed policy, or demand exemption from it. 

**Contact Us**  
Please contact us with your questions or concerns about these privacy policies and/or the practices of this web site at: Smart Publications, PO Box 4667, Petaluma, CA 94955, telephone 1-800-976-2783, or contact us online. 

Copyright © 2008 - Smart Publications  
POB 4667 - Petaluma, CA 94955  
1-800-976-2783  
888-998-6889 (fax) 

| 

Subscribe    
to _Smart Publications  
E-newsletter_  
and receive weekly e-alerts from the world of nutritional medicine.

Just type your email address below and click on submit (unsubscribe anytime.)

Subscribe...to   
_Smart Publications Health & Wellness Update_  
the 16-page monthly newsletter.  
  
and receive the latest information from the world of nutritional medicine.   
>> subscribe for free!

Advertisement  
FREE   
Welcome Kit    
from  
 _Health Freedom Nutrition_ [](http://www.hfn-usa.com/customer-service/catalog.php)   
Complete product listing and discount offers included!  
  
---|---|---
